Lesson 46. Do it yourself. So great is our passion for doing things for ourselves.
第46课。自己做。我们对自己做事的热情是如此之大。
That we are becoming increasingly less dependent on specialized labor.
我们越来越依赖专业劳动。
plead: v.   找（借口），辩解, ignorance: n.   无知，不懂
No one can plead ignorance of a subject any longer.
没有人能再无知。
publication: n.   出版物
For these are countless do it yourself publications.
因为这些是自己的出版物。
Armed with the right tools and materials.
配备正确的工具和材料。
Newly wed Galey embark on the task of decorating their own homes.
新婚盖利（Galey）开始装饰自己的房屋的任务。
leisure: n.   空闲
Men, particularly, spend hours of their leisure time installing their own fireplaces.
尤其是男人，花费数小时的时间安装自己的壁炉。
Laying out their own gardens. Building garages and making furniture.
布置自己的花园。建造车库并制作家具。
keen: adj. 热心的，渴望的
Some really keen enthusiasts go so far as to build their own computers.
一些真正敏锐的爱好者甚至可以构建自己的计算机。
advisory: adj. 咨询的, novice: n.   新手
Shops cater for the do it yourself craze not only by running special advisory services for novices.
商店不仅通过为新手开展特殊的咨询服务来迎合自己的热潮。
consumer: n.   消费者，顾客, assemble: v.   装配，组装
But by offering consumers bits and pieces which they can assemble at home.
但是，通过提供可以在家组装的消费者零碎的东西。
outlet: n.   出路, creative: adj. 创造性的
Such things provide an excellent outlet for pent up creative energy.
这样的事情为抑制创造力的精力提供了绝佳的渠道。
But unfortunately not all of us are born handymen.
但是不幸的是，并非我们所有人都是天生的杂物。
resourceful: adj. 足智多谋的
Some wives tend to believe that their husbands are infinitely resourceful and can fix anything.
一些妻子倾向于相信他们的丈夫无限足智多谋，可以解决任何问题。
Even men who can hardly drive a nail in straight are supposed to be born electricians.
即使是几乎无法驾驶指甲的男人也应该是天生的电工。
fuse: v.   由于烧断保险丝而短路
Carpenters. Plummers and mechanics. When lights fuse.
木匠。水管工和力学。当灯融合时。
rickety: adj. 要散架的，晃动的, clog: v.   堵塞
Furniture gets rickety. Pipes get clogged. Or vacuum cleaners fail to operate.
家具摇摇欲坠。管子被堵塞。或真空吸尘器无法操作。
Some women assume that their husbands will somehow put things right.
一些妇女认为自己的丈夫会以某种方式把事情做对。
delusion: n.   错觉
The worst thing about the do it yourself game is that sometimes even men live under the delusion.
关于自己做的最糟糕的事情是，有时甚至男人都生活在妄想之下。
That they can do anything. Even when they have repeatedly been proved wrong.
他们可以做任何事情。即使他们一再被证明是错误的。
It is a question of pride as much as anything else.
这是一个与其他任何事物一样多的自豪问题。
Last spring my wife suggested that I call in a man to look at our lawn mower.
去年春天，我的妻子建议我打电话给一个男人看我们的割草机。
It had broken down the previous summer. And though I promised to repair it.
它已经破坏了前夏天。尽管我答应修复它。
I had never got around it. I would not hear of the suggestion and said that I would fix it myself.
我从来没有解决过。我不会听到这个建议，并说我会自己修复。
One Saturday afternoon I hauled the machine into the garden and had a close look at it.
一个星期六下午，我将机器拖到花园里，仔细看了看它。
adjustment: n.   调整, screw: n.   螺丝钉
As far as I could see it needed only a minor adjustment. A turn of a screw here.
据我所知，它只需要进行较小的调整。这里的螺丝转弯。
A little tightening up there. A drop of oil and it would be as good as new.
那里有点收紧。一滴油，它和新的一样好。
fuse: v.   由于烧断保险丝而短路
Inevitably the repair job was not quite so simple. The mower firmly refused to mow.
不可避免地，维修工作并不那么简单。割草机坚定地拒绝割草。
dismantle: v.   拆卸, chunk: n.   （厚）块
So I decided to dismantle it. The garden was soon littered with chunks of metal which had once
所以我决定拆除它。花园很快就散布着曾经有过的金属
made up a lawn mower. But I was extremely pleased with myself. I had traced the cause of the trouble.
组成割草机。但是我对自己感到非常满意。我追踪了麻烦的原因。
snap: v.   绷断
One of links in the chain that drives the wheels had snapped.
驱动车轮驱动的链条中的一个链接已经折断。
insurmountable: adj. 不能克服的，难以对付的
After buying a new chain I was faced with the insurmountable task of putting the confusing
购买新连锁店后，我面临着令人困惑的不可或缺的任务
fuse: v.   由于烧断保险丝而短路, jigsaw: n.   线锯
jigsaw. Puzzle together again. I was not surprised to find that the machine still refused to work
拼图。再次拼图。我并不感到惊讶的是，机器仍然拒绝工作
assemble: v.   装配，组装
after I had reassembled it. For the simple reason that I was left with several curiously shaped
我重新组装后。出于简单的原因，我留下了几个好奇的形状
bits of metal which did not. Seemed to fit anywhere. I gave up in despair. The weeks passed and the
没有的金属。似乎适合任何地方。我绝望地放弃了。几周过去了
nag: v.   唠叨不休
grass grew. When my wife nagged me to do something about it. I told her that either I would have to
草生长。当我的妻子na咬我做些事情时。我告诉她，要么我必须
buy a new mower or let the grass grow. Needless to say our house is now surrounded by a jungle.
购买新的割草机或让草生长。不用说我们的房子现在被丛林所包围。
Buried somewhere in deep grass there is a rusting lawn mower which I have promised to repair one.
埋在深草中的某个地方有一个生锈的割草机，我答应修复一个。
Day
天